He is an American citizen
held in solitary in Miami
while strangers online call
for his death
Innocent
until proven guilty
His name is Andrew Tate
You there,
second desk
what is your name?
My name is Alexis.
Alexis,
please leave my lecture room,
I don't understand.
I am not going
to ask a second time,
Tell me,
was I unfair to
your classmate just now?
Indeed I was.
So, why
didn't any of you protest?
you didn't say anything
because you weren't affected
yourself
if you don't help
bring about justice
one day you too
may experience injustice and
there will be nobody
there to stand before you.
You weren't affected
Not yet
Will you stay silent
or stand up for Tate